OLEKSIS BONDARENKO

Front-end developer



ABOUT ME

Hi there! My name is Oleksis. I am a front-end developer. I reall enjoy TypeScript and React. I am solving problems as a single developer and in a team. Well experienced in react, java script, structures and algoritms. Currently live in Kyiv. I want <u>Ukraine</u> to <u>win</u> this WAR! Glory to Ukraine! Glory to Heroes!

P.S. I hope you are in a safe place!



oleksisbondarenko@gmail.com



+380-99-12-3456



OleksiiBondarenko.github.io



github.com/OleksisBondarenko

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Native

English Upper-intermediate

Russian Prizerayu

EDUCATION

Bachelor computer scence (2019 - 2023)

Institute Telecomunication and information, Kyiv

- Algoritms and structures
- Work in a team
- Git / GitHub
- Java Script
- HTML / CSS
- Mongo DB

EXPERIENCE

PA Group (March 2021 - February 2022)

Outsourced company engaged in web development

- My role was creating landing pages using figma. Often i had additional tasks to process data from the server using the built-in fetch or library axios. To provide styles we used css modules and library StyledComponents.
- I used REST / RESTfull api to transfer data between server and client part of the project. As a state manager we used Redux (@Reduxjs/Toolkit) but i also a bit familiar with mobX
- To develop project at the same time our team was using GitHub and GitFlow. I developed pages independently and in the team. Worked with inner logic of an application, requests to the server. Made Docker with nodejs project.

Pet projects, Oleksii Cherevan (2021 - 2022)

My projects on github

- portfolio page
- info about countries
- exchanger
- shop

MY SKILLS

Hard skills

- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- Responsible design / adaptive design / Flex / Grid
- React / Redux
- Gulp / Webpack
- Git / GitHub / GitFlow
- Figma
- Algoritms and structures

Soft skills

- Self motivated
- Responsible
- Reliable
- Do work properly
- Good communicative
- Friendly
- Team player

HOBBIES









Music

Jogging

Electronic

Traveling